http://www.abita.com/contact/privacy-policy

Are You 21 or Older?
Submit
Don't have a login? Sign up here!
Tap Room is Open for Patio Seating! No Tours Just Yet!Click Here for Hours & Holiday Hours! »
Order Online
Tap Room is Open for Patio Seating! No Tours Just Yet! Click Here for Hours & Holiday Hours! »
PRIVACY POLICY
Copyright © 2008 Abita and ABITA.COM, LLC TM. All Right Reserved.
Abita is committed to protecting your privacy. By accessing this website, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement.
Collection of your Personal Information:
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you to provide a service or carry out a transaction that you have requested such as receiving information about Abita products and services, entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site or service, or when purchasing, downloading and/or registering Abita products. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, work e-mail, work phone, work or home address, information about your job function, information about your company, information about circumstances related to your purchase, and payment information.
We may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the site, analyze trends and administer the site.
Control of your Personal Information:
Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the site will not be shared outside of Abita and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission.
Please be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to Abita in the context of other, separately operated, Abita products or services.
ABITA.COM may send out periodic e-mails informing you of issues related to a product or service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service such as invoices and confirmations. In some services offered by ABITA.COM, contact with the customer is a necessary part of the service.
Some services offered on ABITA.COM may collect information that is not accessible to the customer via our website. In such cases, you can access your personal information by contacting ABITA.COM as described at the bottom of this statement, or through alternative means of access described by the service.
Security of your Personal Information:
Abita is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Protection of Children's Personal Information
ABITA.COM does not knowingly collect any personal information from children. It is against our Terms of Use for anyone under 21 to submit data to our site.
Use of Cookies
We may use cookies and/or web beacons on this website to ensure the integrity of the registration process and to personalize the site. Cookies and Web Beacons cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. You can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other Web sites you visit. ABITA.COM prohibits Web Beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.
Unsubscribe Information
Instructions to remove an email address are located on the bottom of every promotional email. Alternatively, unsubscribe requests may be handled using our online unsubscription form.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about the ABITA.COM online privacy policy or its implementation you may contact us at: ABITA.COM Customer Care, Attn: Privacy Policy Issues, PO Box 1510, Abita Springs, LA 70420; or online at friends@ABITA.COM
You may also send an e-mail or letter to the above e-mail or street address requesting access to or correction of your personally identifiable information. For verification purposes please include your first name, last name, e-mail address and the password you use for said ABITA.COM service.
